[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":85475,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":118455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":11821,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":130278,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2382,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":132662,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5 "],"rt":5119,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":137783,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1518,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":139303,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":8223,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":147526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":37991,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":185518,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4624,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":190142,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":2047,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":192190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum  is 6 or  bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3847,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":196038,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1151,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":197190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3704,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":200894,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0 "},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":927,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":201822,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3150,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":204973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1000,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":205974,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember,  to perf orm +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4304,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":210279,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":927,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":211206,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3199,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":214406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":919,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":215326,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3591,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":218918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":911,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":219830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":34661,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":254494,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Simi larly, 3  is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":74078,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":328573,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":8430,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":337005,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1311,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":338317,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of a n elemen t is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":341861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":847,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":342710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2895,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":345605,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correc t! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":903,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":346509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2904,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":349414,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":967,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":350382,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br  /> (Rem ember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3575,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":353958,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":33407,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":387366,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes.  they ad d to make 6.","response_history":["yes. they add to make 6."],"rt":30447,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":417814,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":15271,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":433085,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<su b>6</sub > 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":666996,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1100081,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":15566,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1115649,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using ju st 3.","rt":6519,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1122169,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":45285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1167456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":2544,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1170000,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":24560,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1194561,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":2215,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1196777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":6447,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1203225,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1377,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1204602,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"They all can produce zero.","response_history":[" They all  p;","They all p","They all can produce zero."],"rt":63374,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1267976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":25567,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1293544,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5047,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1298592,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":991,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1299584,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3415,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1303000,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3936,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1306937,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3392,"trial_type":"quest ion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1310329,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2495,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1312825,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":8359,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1321185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The answer is 5. 4 plus 1 is 5. 5 is less than 9, so the answer is 5.","response_history":["4 plu","The answer is 5. 4 plus 1 is 5. 5 is less than 9, so the answer is 5."],"rt":30511,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1351697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9. ","response_history":["3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9. ","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9.","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9, whc","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9, wh","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9, w","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9, ","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9,","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9 which e","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9 which ","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9 which","3. 8 plus  4 is 12.  12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9 whic","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9 whi","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9 wh","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9 w","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9 ","3. 8 plus 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, so subtract 9. "],"rt":34470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1386168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm similarly unsure about +9. would it be whatever numbers add such that a +9 equation equals 0?","response_history":["Was a tad confused on the identity for *","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm not","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm no","Was a tad con fused on  the identity for +6, so I'm n","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm even less sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm even les sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm even le sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm even l sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm even  sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm even sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm eve sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm ev sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm e sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm es sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm e sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm  sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm s sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on t he ident ity for +6, so I'm si sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm sim sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm simi sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm simil sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm similar sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm similarl sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm similarly sure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm similarly usure about +9.","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm similarly unsure about +9. would it be whatever numbers add to ","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm similarly unsure about +9. would it be whatever numbers add to","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm similarly unsure about +9. would it be whatever numbers add t","Was a tad confused on the identity for +6, so I'm similarly unsure about +9. would  it be wh atever numbers add such that a +9 equation equals 0?"],"rt":81960,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1468129,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["it would","4"],"rt":8319,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1476449,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4608,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1481057,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"You need to  add 6 t o 3 in order to get 9 so that you can subtract 9 and get zero. thus, 6 is the needed number.","response_history":["You need to add 6 to 3 int","You need to add 6 to 3 in order to get 9 so that the nu","You need to add 6 to 3 in order to get 9 so that the n","You need to add 6 to 3 in order to get 9 so that the ","You need to add 6 to 3 in order to get 9 so that the","You need to add 6 to 3 in order to get 9 so that th","You need to add 6 to 3 in order to get 9 so that t","You need to add 6 to 3 in order to get 9 so that you can subtract 9 and get zero. thus, 6 is the needed number."],"rt":38192,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1519249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and do +9 operation with 2 successive ly on ea ch answer. When you get to 10, you must subtract nine, which gives you 1. The same is true for every odd number between 0 and 10, and this is suggestive that 2 is a generator for +9","response_history":["12","1","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 is ","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 is","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start wt","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 ","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 ","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and move ","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and move","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and mov","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and mo","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and m","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and ","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and add","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and ad","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8  if you s tart with 2 +9 0 and a","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and do +9 operation with 2 successively on each answer. When you get to 10, you must sube","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and do +9 operation with 2 successively on each answer. When you get to 10, you must subtract nine, which gives you 1. The same is true for every odd number a","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and do +9 operation with 2 successively on each answer. When you get to 10, you must subtract nine, which gives you 1. The same is true for every odd number ","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and do +9 operation with 2 successively on each answer. When you get to 10, you must subtract nine, which gives you 1. The same is true for every odd number betwee ","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and do +9 operation with 2 successively on each answer. When you get to 10, you must subtract nine, which gives you 1. The same i s true f or every odd number between 1","2 give you 2, 4, 6, and 8 if you start with 2 +9 0 and do +9 operation with 2 successively on each answer. When you get to 10, you must subtract nine, which gives you 1. The same is true for every odd number between 0 and 10, and this is suggestive that 2 is a generator for +9"],"rt":164198,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1683448,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9, never creates numbers between 0 and 10 other than 3, 6, and 9.","response_history":["No. It seems that any m","No. It seems that any number that adds to ","No. It seems that any number that adds to","No. It  seems t hat any number that adds t","No. It seems that any number that adds ","No. It seems that any number that adds","No. It seems that any number that add","No. It seems that any number that ad","No. It seems that any number that a","No. It seems that any number that created","No. It seems that any number that create","No. It seems that any number that creats","No. It seems that any number that creates zero wth","No. It seems that any number that creates zero wt","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these ti","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times added s","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times added ","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times added","No. I t seems  that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times adde","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times add","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times ad","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times a","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9 ","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9, never creates the numb","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types  of opera tions is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9, never creates the num","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9, never creates the nu","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9, never creates the n","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9, never creates the ","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9, never creates the","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9, neve r create s th","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9, never creates t","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9, never creates numbers between 0 and 10 other than 2","No. It seems that any number that creates zero with itself under these types of operations is not a generator. 3, no matter how many times operated on with +9, never creates numbers between 0 and 10 other than 3, 6, and 9."],"rt":81208,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1764657,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. It appears that 5 can create the all numbers betwe en 0 and  10, and this has so far been suggestive that it is an operator.","response_history":["No. b","No. Bete","No. Bet","No. Be","No. B","No. 5 is added to ","Yes. It appears that 5 creates ","Yes. It appears that 5 crea","Yes. It appears that 5 cre","Yes. It appears that 5 cr","Yes. It appears that 5 can create the num=","Yes. It appears that 5 can create the num","Yes. It appears that 5 can create the nu","Yes. It appears that 5 can create the n","Yes. It appears that 5 can create the all nbu","Yes. It appears that 5 can create the all nb","Yes. It appears that 5 can create the all numbers between 0 and 10, and this has so far been suggestive that iti","Yes. It appears that 5 can create the all numbers between 0 and 10, and this has so far been suggestive that it is an operator."],"rt":117279,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1881937,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in  words ho w you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. 6 +9 0 = 6. But then 6 +9 6 = 3 and 6 +9 3 = 0. As we discussed, it is almost certain that it is not a generator because it can make 0.","response_history":["No. 6 + ","No. 6 +9 0 + ","No. 6 +9 0 +","No. 6 +9 0 = 6. But then ","No. 6 +9 0 = 6. But then 6 +9 6 = 3 and 6 +9 3 = 0. As we sd","No. 6 +9 0 = 6. But then 6 +9 6 = 3 and 6 +9 3 = 0. As we s","No. 6 +9 0 = 6. But then 6 +9 6 = 3 and 6 +9 3 = 0. As we dii","No. 6 +9 0 = 6. But then 6 +9 6 = 3 and 6 +9 3 = 0. As we discuse","No. 6 +9 0 = 6. But then 6 +9 6 = 3 and 6 +9 3 = 0. As we discussed, th","No. 6 +9 0 = 6. But then 6 +9 6 = 3 and 6 +9 3 = 0. As we discussed, t","No. 6 +9 0 = 6. But then 6 +9 6 = 3 and 6 +9 3 = 0. As we discussed, it is almost certain that it is not a generator because it can make 0."],"rt":99976,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1981913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":35783,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2017697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 +n (n - 1) = 0","response_history":["1 +n (n - 1_","1 +n (n - 1) = 0"],"rt":27135,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2044833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero x and the other number must add to n. The way to guarantee this is by subtracting n from x to arrive at the other number.","response_history":["x + ","x +n (x-n). ","x +n (x-n).","x +n (x-n) = 0. We no","x +n (x-n) = 0. We n","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the ni","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the n","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the e;","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero. Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero . Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by. Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inv erse mus t add with the element, x, to make zero by . Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by d. Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by de. Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by def. Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by defi. Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by defin. Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by defini. Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definiti. Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definitio. Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. Thus","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know t hat the  inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. Thu","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. Th","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. T","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know taht","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know tah","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know ta","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that ii","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in order to acheive th","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by defin ition. W e also know that in order to acheive t","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in order to acheive ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in order to acheive","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in order to acheiv","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in order to achei","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in order to ache","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in order to achievv","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in  order t o achieve ths ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in order to achieve ths","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in order to achieve thii","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in order to achieve this with any given element","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that in","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that i","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n wl","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that  the inv erse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted wi","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted w","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element adds with another number to ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element adds ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element adds","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element add","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add wi th the e lement, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element ad","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element a","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with the ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with the","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with th","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element  has the  operation with t","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with another number such at","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with another number such a","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with another number such that the elemn","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with another number such that the elem","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n  will be  subtracted if the given element has the operation with another number such that the ele","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with another number such that the el","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with another number such that the e","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with another number such that the ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with another number ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with  the ele ment, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has the operation with another number","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has t","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element has","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element ha","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element h","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know tha t the in verse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and its ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and its","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and it","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and i","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and","x +n (x-n) = 0. We  know tha t the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element an","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element a","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element i","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element add","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element ad","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal a ","x +n ( x-n) = 0 . We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal a","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero m","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero x ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero x and the other number must add to n. The was","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the e lement,  x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero x and the other number must add to n. The way to guarantee this is by subtracting n frfom ","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero x and the other number must add to n. The way to guarantee this is by subtracting n frfom","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero x and the other number must add to n. The way to guarantee this is by subtracting n frfo","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero b y defini tion. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero x and the other number must add to n. The way to guarantee this is by subtracting n frf","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero x and the other number must add to n. The way to guarantee this is by subtracting n from x to arrive tat","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero x and the other number must add to n. The way to guarantee this is by subtracting n from x to arrive ta","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero  by defi nition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero x and the other number must add to n. The way to guarantee this is by subtracting n from x to arrive t","x +n (x-n) = 0. We know that the inverse must add with the element, x, to make zero by definition. We also know that n will be subtracted if the given element and the other number equal n or greater. Therefore, in order to get zero x and the other number must add to n. The way to guarantee this is by subtracting n from x to arrive at the other number."],"rt":260630,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2305465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"You see whether it can make 0. If it can, it is not a generator. ","response_history":["You see wheter ","You see wheter","You see whete","You see whether it can make 0. If it ga","You see whether it can make 0. If it gca","You see whether it can make 0. If it gc","You see whether it can make 0. If it g","You see whether it can make 0. If it can, it is not a generator. "],"rt":27966,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2333432,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":9079,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2342512,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"mu lti","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6031,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2348544,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":20935,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2369480,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is s ubtracte d. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, successive operations will play a loop of repeating responses. Thus, such a number could not produce all numbers, only those within the loop.","response_history":["A n","A gn","A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. ","TA generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. ","TrA generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. ","TruA generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. ","TrueA generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n,  ","True. A generator of  +n shoul d be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n  ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n i ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is  ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is s ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is su ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is sub ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is sube ","True.  A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is sub ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is subt ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is subtr ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is subtra ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is subtrac ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is subtract ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is  added t o itself enough times to exceed +n, n is subtracte ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to exceed +n, n is subtracted ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to eexceed +n, n is subtracted ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equexceed +n, n is subtracted ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equaexceed +n, n is subtracted ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal exceed +n, n is subtracted ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal oexceed +n, n i s subtra cted ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed +n, n is subtracted ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If ti","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If t","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If it is ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n,  n is sub tracted. If it is","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If it i","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If it ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If it","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If i","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the answer ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enou gh times  to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the answer","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the answe","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the answ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the ans","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the an","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the a","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with  only it self and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the ru","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the reul","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the reu","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, the ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successie","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x  is added  to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successie","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. h","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that iit","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is  greater  than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that iit","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that ii","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it ea","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough  times t o equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, the ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, the","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps . Howeve r, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, th","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, t","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, suz","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. Whe n x is a dded to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, successively ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, successively","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue  to gene rate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, successivel","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, successive","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, successive operations will  b","True . A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, successive operations will play a loop of repeating responses. Thus, such an ","True. A generator of +n should be able to make all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, successive operations will play a loop of repeating responses. Thus, such an","True. A generator of +n should be ab le to ma ke all numbers with only itself and 0. When x is added to itself enough times to equal or exceed n, n is subtracted. If the resulting answer is greater than 0, then when x is added successively it will continue to generate unique solutions that fill in gaps. However, if x is ever added in such a way that it equals n, the result will be zero. In effect, successive operations will play a loop of repeating responses. Thus, such a number could not produce all numbers, only those within the loop."],"rt":533135,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2902616,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":65847,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2968465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Always. The number will just be another 'step' in the previous one, and will therefore reflect the same pattern.","response_history":["Always. The number is ","Always. The number is","Always. The number i","Always. The number will b","Always. The number will just be a n","Always. The number will just be a ","Always. The number will just be another 'step' in the previous one.","Always. The number will just be another 'step' in the previous one, and th","Always. The number will just be another 'step' in the previous one, and t","Always. The number will just be another 'step' in the previous one, and will therefore reflcec","Always. The numbe r will j ust be another 'step' in the previous one, and will therefore reflce","Always. The number will just be another 'step' in the previous one, and will therefore reflc","Always. The number will just be another 'step' in the previous one, and will therefore reflect the same pattern."],"rt":545446,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":3513912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":11807,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":3525720,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2215,"trial_type":"in structio ns","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":3527936,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"31","response_history":["31"],"rt":2441,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":3530377,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":2839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":3533216,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and  you're  not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever passed. Was pretty distracted by life at the time.","response_history":["Hm. I took ","Hm. I took","Hm. I too","Hm. I to","Hm. I t","Hm. I ","Hm. I","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever aps","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever ap","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever a","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever passed. For some reason, I do better with math in this format than e","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever passed. For some reason, I do better with math in this format than lectures.","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever passed. ","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think  I ever  passed. wa","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever passed. w","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever passed. Was pretty distracted by life at thet","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever passed. Was pretty distracted by life at thet","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever passed. Was pretty distracted by life at the tie","Hm. I suppose algebra or trig? Took Calc, but I don't think I ever passed. Was pretty distracted by life at the time."],"rt":92429,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":3625647,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand  it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":6543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":3632191,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4040,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":3636232,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":[" 1 - not  at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4966,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":3641199,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3239,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":3644439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":1912,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":3646352,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":" What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2127,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":3648480,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4887,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":3653368,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.","response_history":["NO.","NO","No."],"rt":7191,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":3660560,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you h ave any  comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"This was truly fun. ","response_history":["This was truly fun. "],"rt":7567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":3668128,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]